"lang"
{
"Language" "English"
"Tokens"
{
"nro_hint_0"	"“Right now? The one where you try and argue with an autistic 2 year old brick wall named Sader.”\n― Ｋａｋｋｏｉｉ"
"nro_hint_1"	"“No more autism threads. A thread for off-topic but not spam posts is allowed.”\n― TheKindredPhantom"
"nro_hint_2"	"“what if i'll record myself playing blade symphony and crying furiously accompanied by beethoven's moonlight sonata”\n― Mindless⚔Solitude"
"nro_hint_3"	"“I locked this thread because everybody I hate has responded to it before me.“ \n― urinal-cake"
"nro_hint_4"	"“lol redmunds whole premise is that its our job as developers to be mature, im pretty sure our only job is to make a game.”\n ― Termi"
"nro_hint_5"	"“someone no one likes is banned from a server what a shocker”\n― deef"
"nro_hint_6"	"“Hey guys, I'm going to be trying to work on creating a $500 prize pool World Tournament for the next patch.”\n― Water"
"nro_hint_7"	"“Sader's on his period again, just like I was a few months back. It ebbs and flows like the river tides.”\n― Jester"
"nro_hint_8"	"“Who do you think is the most quotable Blade Symphony player?”\n― Chaotic"
"nro_hint_9"	"“Yes matt, lets sugjest ideas that will make people want to murder you in your sleep after fighting you.”\n― Sader"
"nro_hint_10"	"“You digusting plebians neglected to worship me, Sader, God-King of the Workshop...You don't deserve the handcrafted items of a deity.”\n― Sader's Ego"
"nro_hint_11"	"“your mom was professional”\n- GRIMNARR"
"nro_hint_12"	"“This is definitely an A+ troll though, I am in stitches He called me a swine lmao”\n― Coldhands"	
"nro_hint_13"	"“it doesnt matter i'm #1”\n― Whoarts"
"nro_hint_14"	"“Nothing was quite as enjoyable as slowly sliding into the view of the Battlechess crowd as someone was trying to explain the rules”\n― Sentient"
"nro_hint_15"	"“I personally like how america is becoming more aware / accepting of japanese culture, although I wouldnt want shit to go full weeb”\n― Xehanoth"
"nro_hint_16"	"“actually he is, hali is my lennynigga (͡°͜ʖ͡°)”\n- raffle"
"nro_hint_18"	"“Redmund m8, I can probably use your mother  as a barbell while squatting.”\n- Stg. Stoner"
"nro_hint_19"	"“This thread has truly enlightened my view of the world.”\n- YujiYuji"
"nro_hint_20"	"“Pure's skeleton is fucked seven ways from sunday for the sake of making her butt pop.”\n- Xehanoth"
"nro_hint_21"	"“And this is why constructive criticism just doesn't seem to work here...”\n- Sear"
"nro_hint_22"	"“i want to die.”\n- deef"
"nro_hint_23"	"“I'm done.“\n- TheKindredPhantom"
"nro_hint_24"	"“there are people who actually appreciate this game's community?”\n- Ashelin"
"nro_hint_25"	"“I dare say only a maximum of 5 players have actually touched (if not just mearly poked) level 3 in blade symphony.”\n- Whoarts"
"nro_hint_26"	"“Also am I not a quotable person? Am I not cool enough to be quoted? I should probably just off myself in that case.”\n- Jahka"
"nro_hint_27"	"“im gay irl”\n- Water"
"nro_hint_28"	"“don't worry soon enough you can use fluxbux to change your character model into your favorite cartoon character and roleplay away.”\n- Ashelin"
"nro_hint_29"	"“I only made this stupid mod to get featured on the workshop again. ps. ASCII gets so fucked up when its put into these quotes.\n- Nero"
"nro_hint_30"	"“Lasermaxx don't multipost, your post has an edit function, use it.“\n- TheKindredPhantom"
"nro_hint_31"	"“lol, this is a FANTASTIC thread. I love it.“n\- urinal-cake"
"nro_hint_32"	"“My Shitpost.“\n- Mike, innocent victim of the forum Nazis"
"nro_hint_33"	"You are a fucking cunt that might as well commit seppuku for how fucking autistic you are. Go back to your fucking mental ward you prick.\n- Ｋａｋｋｏｉｉ"
}
}